http://www.progressive-concepts.com/privacy.html

Items | Total: $0.00
HomeParts AM Transmitters Enclosures Heat Sinks Power Supplies Specialty FM Transmitters Stereo Generators Transistors Voltage Regulators Studio Audio Codecs Automation Software Audio Enhancers Audio Solutions CD Players Digital Processors Effects Processors Equalizers FM Receivers Headphone Amplifiers Headphones Microphone Booms Microphones On-Air Mixing Consoles Patch Bays Portable Mixers Production Mixing Boards Profanity Delays RDS Encoders Stereo Generators Stereo Limiters Telephone Hybrids Voice Processor Warning Lights Wireless Audio Interface Test Equipment AM Receivers Antenna Analyzer Dummy Loads Modulation Monitors Power Meters RDS Reader Spectrum Analyzers FM Receivers Transmission AM Antennas AM Transmitters Bandpass Filters Coaxial Cable Emergency Alert Systems FM Antennas FM Transmitters Low Pass Filters LPFM Transmitters Part 15 Transmitters Power Dividers RF Adaptors RF Amplifiers RF Connectors Specialty FM Transmitters STL Transmitters Surge Suppressors Towers ClearanceOnline CatalogPC Prime
Privacy Policy Your privacy is of great importance to us.   Because we gather certain types of information about users of Progressive Concepts, we feel that you should fully understand the terms and conditions regarding the capture and use of information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.   Registration   Progressive Concepts uses registration forms. Registration forms require users to give us contact information, like names and e-mail addresses, as well as identifiers, like IDs and passwords. The user's contact information is used to facilitate order processing for purchases in the future, as well as to contact users about specials and promotions. Individual user information is never disclosed to third parties.   Order forms   Progressive Concepts uses an order form for customers to purchase products. If you place an order at Progressive Concepts, we will collect information from you, including your contact information and credit card information for credit card orders. This information will be used by Progressive Concepts to bill you for products. Contact information from the order form will also be used to ship orders, to contact you for customer service related issues, and to send you information about our company   Cookies   Progressive Concepts uses a feature of your Internet Web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Progressive Concepts creates and then uses these cookie files to track your movement "clicks" as you move around the Progressive Concepts web site.   Progressive Concepts only uses cookies to keep track of items you put into your shopping cart and to help determine whether you came to Progressive Concepts from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement.   Cookies can also be used to help save and retrieve usernames used on the Progressive Concepts website. This is done for convenience and means that you do not have to re-enter this information on every visit to Progressive Concepts. Cookies cannot be used by Progressive Concepts to retrieve any personal information about you unless you have previously purchased from or registered with us. Progressive Concepts does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you.   Security   Progressive Concepts uses the latest secure transaction processing methods available for web commerce applications. Progressive Concepts has obtained its Secure Server ID from Thawte. Thawte Certification, a VeriSign company, is a global provider of digital certificate products, services and solutions that create security, privacy and authentication in electronic commerce.   Progressive Concepts uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) for all encrypted transactions. SSL ensures that your personal information and credit card data is secure when shopping at Progressive Concepts.
Contact Us & Request A Catalog
* Indicates required information
Name *
First
Last
Company Name
Company Name
Address *
Address Line 1
Address Line 2
Address Line 3
Country *
Country
Select
UNITED STATESALAND ISLANDSALBANIAALGERIAAMERICAN SAMOAANDORRAANGOLAANGUILLAANTIGUA & BARBUDAARGENTINAARMENIAARUBAAUSTRALIAAUSTRIAAZERBAIJANAZORESBAHAMASBAHRAINBANGLADESHBARBADOSBELARUSBELGIUMBELIZEBENINBERMUDABHUTANBOLIVIABONAIREBOSNIABOTSWANABRAZILTORTOLABRUNEIBULGARIABURKINA FASOBURUNDICAMBODIACAMEROONCANADACANARY ISLANDSCAPE VERDECAYMAN ISLANDSCENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLICCHADCHILECHINACOLOMBIACONGOCOOK ISLANDSCOSTA RICACROATIACURACAOCYPRUSCZECH REPUBLICDEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGODENMARKDJIBOUTIDOMINICADOMINICAN REPUBLICECUADOREGYPTEL SALVADORENGLANDEQUATORIAL GUINEAERITREAESTONIAETHIOPIAFAEROE ISLANDSFIJIFINLANDFRANCEFRENCH GUIANAFRENCH POLYNESIAGABONGAMBIAGEORGIAGERMANYGHANAGIBRALTARGREECEGREENLANDGRENADAGUADELOUPEGUAMGUATEMALAGUERNSEYGUINEAGUINEA-BISSAUGUYANAHAITIHOLLANDHONDURASHONG KONGHUNGARYICELANDINDIAINDONESIAIRAQIRELANDISRAELITALYIVORY COASTJAMAICAJAPANJERSEYJORDANKAZAKHSTANKENYAKIRIBATIKOSRAEKUWAITKYRGYZSTANLAOSLATVIALEBANONLESOTHOLIBERIALIBYALIECHTENSTEINLITHUANIALUXEMBOURGMACAUMACEDONIA(FYROM)MADAGASCARMADEIRAMALAWIMALAYSIAMALDIVESMALIMALTAMARSHALL ISLANDSMARTINIQUEMAURITANIAMAURITIUSMEXICOMICRONESIAMOLDOVAMONACOMONGOLIAMONTSERRATMOROCCOMOZAMBIQUEN. MARIANA ISLANDSNAMIBIANEPALNETHERLANDSNETHERLANDS ANTILLESNEW CALEDONIANEW ZEALANDNICARAGUANIGERNIGERIANORFOLK ISLANDNORTHERN IRELANDNORWAYOMANPAKISTANPALAUPANAMAPAPUA NEW GUINEAPARAGUAYPERUPHILIPPINESPOLANDPONAPEPORTUGALPUERTO RICOQATARREUNIONROMANIAROTARUSSIARWANDASABASAIPANSAN MARINOSAUDI ARABIASCOTLANDSENEGALYUGOSLAVIASEYCHELLESSIERRA LEONESINGAPORESLOVAKIASLOVENIASOLOMON ISLANDSSOUTH AFRICASOUTH KOREASPAINSRI LANKAST. BARTHELEMYST. CHRISTOPHERST. CROIXST. EUSTATIUSST. JOHNST. KITTS & NEVISST. LUCIAST. MAARTENST. MARTINST. THOMASST. VINCENT/GRENADINESSURINAMESWAZILANDSWEDENSWITZERLANDSYRIATAHITITAIWANTAJIKISTANTANZANIATHAILANDTIMOR LESTETINIANTOGOTONGATRINIDAD & TOBAGOTRUKTUNISIATURKEYTURKMENISTANTURKS & CAICOS ISLANDSTUVALUUGANDAUKRAINEUNION ISLANDUNITED ARAB EMIRATESUNITED KINGDOMURUGUAYUS VIRGIN ISLANDSUZBEKISTANVANUATUVATICAN CITY STATEVENEZUELAVIETNAMVIRGIN GORDAWALESWALLIS & FUTUNA ISLANDSWESTERN SAMOAYAPYEMENZAMBIAZIMBABWE
City *
City
State *
State
Select
AA - MilitaryAE - MilitaryAP - MilitaryAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaVirgin IslandsWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingAlbertaBritish ColumbiaLabradorManitobaBrunswickNewfoundlandNova ScotiaNorthwest TerritoriesOntarioPrince Edward IslandQuebecSaskatchewanYukon Territory
Zip/Postal Code *
Zip
-
Zip Ext
Email *
Email
Phone # *
Mobile Phone
Message
Message
Enter code in image:
(630) 736-9822
Progressive Concepts
305 South Bartlett Road - Streamwood, IL 60107
HomeAboutTestimonialsFAQClient FeedbackIndustry NewsPrivacyContact/SupportOrderingLeasingShopping CartMy AccountPC PrimeLayaway Program
The contents of this webpage are Copyright © 2020 Progressive Concepts. All Rights Reserved.
Specialties: Radio Transmitters, Radio Broadcasting Equipment, Sound Mixer, FM Transmitters, Audio Equipment, FM Broadcast Transmitter, FM Radio Transmitter, FM Broadcast Antenna, Low Power FM Transmitter, Low Power Transmitter, Low Power FM Antenna, FM Receiver, FM Antenna, AM Transmitter, AM Radio Transmitter, AM Receiver, Radio Station Equipment, Radio Electronics, Broadcast Electronics, Music Production Equipment, Mixer Board, Mixing Board
Web Design -
Manage
